翻译：bazinga   CS小明漫画家  胡好时  foxer  鱼骨头
校对：原子蛋    总监   原子蛋
后期：加森     时间轴：sagelibra  今
南方公园  第十七季第九集
魔龙的奶舞
《南方公园》
前情回顾
我们马上就要展开有生以来最惨烈的战斗
Soon we will be the fighting the greatest battle of our lives.
黑色星期五
Black Friday.
想要PS4的人  加入我们这边
Everyone who wants to get PS4s, join with us.
你不能死  大家真的很喜欢你
You can't die everybody really likes you.
我们才不会被叛徒贱人肯尼打败呢
We're not going to be beat by the traitor whore Kenny.
战况如此一边倒似乎是一种耻辱
Seems a shame that the fight will be so one-sided.
然后找乔治・马丁问到答案
Go seek out George R. R. Martin for answers.
他就是《权力的游戏》的作者
He's the guy who write Game of Thrones.
你当上加拿大健卫部长
You started as the Canadian minister of health
三个月后  你太太开始朝你阴吹
and 3 months later your wife queefed in your face.
这必将是一场操蛋的血战  汤姆
This is gonna be a f*cking bloodbath Tom.
鸡鸡  鸡鸡鸡鸡  鸡鸡鸡鸡*
*Wiener. Wiener. Wiener. Wiener. Wiener. Wiener. Wiener
两只鸡鸡傍地走*
*One wiener next to another wiener
三只鸡鸡好朋友*
*Two wieners alongside yet another wiener
软鸡鸡  松趴趴  不举鸡鸡*
*Soft wieners, nice and soft, non-erect wieners
弹鸡鸡  弹鸡鸡  弹鸡鸡*
*Flopping wieners, flopping wieners...
肯尼公主
不好了  微软封锁了我们船只的去路
是吗
很快  船就完全不能通行了
黑色星期五就要来了
是个问题
现在  要是肯尼公主在  就好了
我回来了
肯尼公主拜见
出现了
肯尼公主好可爱
肯尼公主  感谢你的到访
有个麻烦
Xbox的船封锁了我的PS4的船只
船运停止了
明白  肯尼公主来帮忙
难道是要封锁我们
快看  是肯尼公主
各位  肯尼来了
他干吗了
He did what?
他跳伞空降  然后干吗了
He flew down in a parachute and did what?
然后他阻止了微软
Apparently he's stopped Microsoft
对PS4船运到购物中心的封锁
from blockading the shipment of PS4s to the mall.
看来他现在四处奔走
It looks like he's all over the place
为索尼赢机型大战啊
winning the console wars for Sony.
凭  凭什么  就凭他可爱
Because... because what? Because he's cute?
卡特曼  他让所有人都站在索尼一边了
Cartman, he's got everyone on Sony's side.
我们阻止不了他
We can't stop him.
但是除了装可爱他还干了什么
But what's he do besides that he's cute?
亲爱的  比尔・盖茨打电话找你
Sweetie, Bill Gates is on the phone for you.
你叫比尔・盖茨一边玩蛋去
Tell Bill Gates to suck my ass mom.
妈  你别真叫比尔・盖茨去玩蛋
Mom, don't seriously tell Bill Gates to suck my ass,
跟他说一切安好
tell him that everything is cool
待会儿我给他回电话
and I'll call him in a little bit.
要是你一开始就让肯尼当他的公主
This wouldn't have ever happened if you would have let him be a princess
就不会有这些事了
in the first place.
他不是公主  他是个汉子
He's not a princess, he's a dude.
不幸的是  他现在是对手了
Well, unfortunately for us he's now on the other side.
我们别无选择了
We're out of options.
你想说什么  凯尔
So what are you saying, Kyle?
我有个主意
I have an idea.
我也不想这样  但恐怕这是唯一的选择了
I dont like it, but I think it's the only choice we have.
黑色星期五  南方公园购物中心
汤姆  黑色星期五终于要到了
Tom, black Friday is finally almost here
如你所见  我身后的假日购物者已失去耐心
and as you can see behind me holiday shoppers are really getting antsy.
人们从感恩节半夜就等在这了
People have been waiting here since midnight on Thanksgiving.
他们饥寒交迫
They are cold, they are starving
在节日酬宾活动中  已经发生多起流血事件
and there's already been a lot of bloodshed over these holiday deals.
有请瑞克・泰尔默  他已经在这守了六天了
Joining me now is Rick Tellmor who's been here for 6 days,
你五岁的儿子被吃掉了  是真的吗
and your five-year-old son was eaten, is that correct?
是的  是的没错  我们不得不吃了他
Yes, yes, that's right, we had to eat him,
我们都开始饿得不行了
we're all started to starve out here,
所以我们抽签  他抽到了死签
so we drew straws and he drew the shortest one.
黑色星期五到来的时候  你想买什么呢
What is you hoping to get when blace Friday does finally start.
蓝光播放机
A blu-rayplaying.
96%的降幅  折后是20美元
96% off, and it's gonna be about 20$.
现在有人可能会说
Now some people might say
吃自己的孩子不太符合圣诞的感觉
that eating your child is not very christmassy.
对他们你想说点什么呢
What would you say to them?
我为播放机吃孩子  还要哈哈笑*
*I ate my son for a blu-ray player with a ho, ho, ho
还要把铃摇*
*and a jingle jingle jingle
儿子吃下肚  味道很不俗*
*My son got aten and he tasted good
还要哈哈笑  还要把铃摇*
*Ho, ho, jingle, jingle ho-ho
无疑  南方公园购物中心的圣诞节活跃而美好
No doubt Christmas is alive and well at the South Park mall.
现场的情况就是这样  汤姆
Back to you, Tom.
弟兄们  计划是这样的
Ok guys, here is the deal.
购物中心大门已经被成千的等待购物者堵死了
The main entrance in the mall is already blocked by thousands of waiting shoppers.
而想要Xbox的小孩打算从左侧翼突入
The kids who want Xboxes plan to flank from the left,
这里
here.
想第一个进入购物中心  最好的办法
Our best chance being frist inside
就是找到一条能到达最后面入口的路
is finding a way to the most back entrance,
这里
here.
"红罗宾"餐厅
At Red Robin.
没错
That's right.
"红罗宾"里面的门
Red Robin has doors on the inside
穿过去正好是购物中心里
that go right out into the mall.
不论谁想第一个进去
The kid asks being the frist one is inside
都要在黑色星期五之前拿下"红罗宾"
is taking over the Red Robin before blace Friday starts.
我们怎么拿下"红罗宾"呢
So how do we take over Red Robin?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
打搅一下
Excuse me.
什么事
Yes.
Xbox的战士来了
The Xbox fighters are here
他们说  想叛队
and they say they want to switch sides.
什么
What?
直接跟他说  卡特曼
Go ahead and tell him, Cartman.
好吧
Alright.
我们代表所有Xbox的战士们
On behalf of the Xbox fighters of Zaron,
在此放下武器  我们放弃了  行了吧
we hereby lay down our arms. We give up. OK?
闭嘴  克雷格  这是个艰难的决定
Shut up, Craig. It's very difficult.
你们赢了  行了吧
You guys win, all right?
我们都玩PS4吧
We all play on Playstations 4s.
虽然我们还是觉得Xbox更棒
We still think Xbox is a superior machine,
但你们这边人太多了
but you guys have too many people on your side,
而且肯尼成了日本的公主
and Kenny became a Japanese princess.
这点太出乎意料了
Nobody saw that coming.
听着  现实情况是
Look, the truth is,
你们知道我们面临着更大的问题
we all have a bigger problem now and you know it.
要是我们不齐心协力的话
Nobody's going to get anything
我们没法在其他数千名消费者中抢到任何东西
if we don't work together against those thousands of other shoppers.
拿到PS4总比什么都没有强  是吗
So better a PS4 than nothing, is that it?
我们还是靠自己算了
I think we'll take our chances on our own.
我们知道怎么进红罗宾
We know a way inside the Red Robin.
你不会以为只有你想到了吧
You don't think you're the only one who thought of it.
我们原本也打算利用红罗宾的入口
We were going to use the red robin entrance too
而且我们想到了方法
and we figured out how.
红罗宾是可以出租的
Red Robin can be rented out,
用作婚礼会场
for wedding parties.
大家都出点钱
If we all chip in,
就可以凑够举行婚礼的保证金了
we can pay for the deposit to have a wedding party there.
这办法可行
Hey. That could work.
咱们一起干吧
Let's do this together, dude.
要想玩新一代游戏机  只有团结合作
Our only shot of playing any next gen console is by teaming up.
要是你想玩PS4
If you want to game on a PS4,
那我也玩
then I do too.
你确定你能接受吗
And you swear you'd be okay with that?
再也不说Xbox更好了吗
You won't ever talk about the Xbox being better ever again?
斯坦  我发誓
I swear, Stan.
好吧伙计们  咱们得计划一场婚礼了
All right guys. Looks like we have got a wedding to plan.
大事不妙
这个机型之战还远远没有结束
是啊
Xbox和PS4的销量不相上下
各位  不要紧的
肯尼公主会更加努力
肯尼酱  打搅一下
有一封给你的婚礼请柬  请看一下
婚礼吗
邀请您参加在红罗宾餐厅的婚礼
肯尼酱  请速归
Kenny, please come home at once.
我们两家不再对抗了
Our two houses have found peace.
快来红罗宾餐厅的婚礼
Come to the Red Robin wedding
我们都将承认您公主的身份
and we'll all accept you as the princess you are.
此致敬礼  巫师王
Yours truly, the wizard king.
太厉害了
肯尼公主要去参加婚礼了
肯尼公主  感谢你所做的一切
多保重呀  肯尼酱
肯尼公主  再见
大家  再见
现在肯尼公主就要回到朋友们的身边去了
怎么回事
肯尼公主死了
真的呢  肯尼公主死了
快看
肯尼公主  不要紧哦
哇哦  好可爱哦
斯坦爵士  我想和你谈谈婚礼的事情
Sir Stan, I was hoping I could talk to you about the wedding.
没问题  怎么了
Yeah, sure. What about it?
等商场开门了  我觉得你待在
I think it's best when the time comes for the mall to open,
离门稍远的地方比较好
you should stay back a bit from the doors.
为什么
Why?
想想看
Well, think about it.
最先进去的人将要承受
The first people inside gonna have to take on
从主入口进入的其他消费者的冲击
the brunt from the holiday shoppers from the main entrance.
让巴特斯和斯考特・梅尔・金森先进去比较好
It's best we let Butters and Scott Mal Kinson go first.
当他们战斗时  我们就可以溜进去了
While they fight, we can simply slip on by.
是有那么些道理
I guess that make scence,
但是巴特斯和斯考特就拿不到PS4了
but Butters and Scott won't be able to get their PS4s.
确实是这样  但是
Yes, that's true. But...
面对现实吧  斯坦爵士
That's face it, sir Stan.
这其实就只关于你和我得到PS
This is all about you and me getting playstations.
其他人的存在只是为了帮我们...
The rest are simply there to help us get through...
他是骗你的
He's lying to you.
他们是假装放弃了  但实际是在骗你
They're just acting like they're giving up but it's a double-bluff.
靠
Dude.
他们会在红罗宾婚礼上背叛你的
They're going to betray you at the Red Robin wedding.
他照搬了《权力的游戏》里面的点子
He got the idea watching Game of Thrones.
我靠  给老子闭嘴
Dude, shut the fuck up.
他是谁
Who is that?
就一个疯老头
He's just an old crazy guy
他不喜欢我在他的花园里玩
who gets pissed off because I was in his garden all the time.
他们会把你关起来的
They're gonna lock you in.
我嘞个操嘞  闭嘴
God damn it. Shut up.
他在我的花园里和另外三人说过同样的话
He talked about it in my garden to like three other people.
他们会把你关在红罗宾
They're gonna lock you in the Red Robin
然后去买Xbox
and then go get all the Xboxes,
所以他才希望你离门远一点
that's why he wants you to stay back from the doors.
你怎么不去干跟全世界说啊
Well, why don't you just tell the whole world everything, hum?
既然你在看《普罗米修斯》
Why don't you tell everybody what Prometheus was about
告诉大家它讲什么啊
while you are at it?
凯尔知道这件事吗
Did Kyle know about this?
伙计  别这样  我们不会背叛你的
Dude, we're not gonna betray you, come on.
你看过《普罗米修斯》了吗
Did you see Prometheus?
我觉得编剧都不知道自己在编啥
I don't think the writer even knew what that is about.
凯尔到底知不知情
Did Kyle know about this?
这就是凯尔的主意
Kyle thought of it.
斯坦  哥们  等一下
Stan. Dude, hold on.
Xbox ONE超赞的
Xbox one is fucking sweet, dude.
你个大混蛋
You're a fucking asshole.
草  滚出我家花园
Fuck you. Get out of my garden.
我拉你一泡屎
I'll shit in your fuckin garden.
去死吧
Go fuck yourself.
经过漫长等待  黑色星期五终于到来了
Well, the wait is over and Black Friday is finally here.
奈尔斯・劳森正在现场  时候到了  奈尔斯
Niles Lawson is at the scene. And it's about time, Niles.
没错  汤姆
That's right, Tom.
商场经理说他们已准备就绪
Mall officials have said they are ready,
大门在嘉宾剪彩之后
and doors will open as soon as their guest of honor
就会打开
cuts the ceremonial red ribbon.
今年的剪彩嘉宾是乔治・马丁
This year's ribbon cutter is of course George R. Martin
他似乎还没抵达现场
who doesn't appear to have shown up yet,
但据说正在赶来的路上
but says he is on his way,
正如他书中始终在路上的龙和僵尸们
just like the dragons and zombies in his novels he is on his way.
等一下
Now just hold on a minute.
我很确定骑马不是去科罗拉多最快的方式
I'm pretty damn sure the fastest way back to Colorado isn't on a horse back.
的确  但是马有其他交通工具
That may be true but horses have one quality that is unmatched
无法比拟的特点
by any other mode of transportation.
是什么
What's that?
百年好合
很好
Okay. Cool.
能面对面摆两个草坪长桌吗
Can we set up the two lawn tables like facing each other,
然后这里摆一个给新郎新娘
and then another for the bride and groom back there.
我听到一个八卦
I heard a rumor.
能问一下吗
May I ask?
是谁要结婚啊
Who's this that's getting married?
汤姆・汉克斯和碧昂丝
Tom Hanks and Beyonce.
是真的吗  真的吗
It's real? It's for real?
天啊  我好爱他们的
Oh my god. I love them.
我也爱
Yeah. Me too.
所以碧昂丝跟Jay Z分手了吗
So Beyonce's not with Jay-Z any more?
很明显啊  不然她也不会
Well, clearly or she wouldn't be
在红龙虾餐厅跟汤姆・汉克斯结婚啊
marrying Tom Hanks at Red Lobster if she was.
伙计们  不要那张桌子
Guys, guys, not that table.
去拿好的来
Get the good tables.
这可是贵宾  好嘛
This is VIP. Ok?
有谁知道巴特斯和斯考特死哪去啦
Has anyone heard from Butters and Scott? Where the fuck are they?
卡特曼
Cartman,
我听说斯坦识破我们的计划了
I heard that Stan somehow found out about our plan.
是的
Yes, he did.
你到底要干嘛
What the hell are you doing?
这下要失败了
This is not gonna work now?
没关系  凯尔
It's fine, Kyle.
一切都在掌控之中
Everything has been taken care of.
斯坦不会再跟任何人有任何交流了
Stan won't be telling anybody anything ever again.
你个猪做了什么
What the hell did you do?
做了该做的  这样我们才能
What had to be done so that we can
用Xbox玩游戏  凯尔
play our games on Xboxes, Kyle.
别跟我说你真那样做啊
No. Tell me you didn't.
他不可以出来
He's not allowed to come out of his room,
所以你就隔着门跟他说吧
so you can talk to him through the door.
谢谢  马什女士
Thanks, Mrs. Marsh.
长话短说  他这次惹的麻烦大了
And keep it short. He's in real trouble.
竟敢在一个好心大爷的花园里大便
He defecated in a nice old man's garden.
好的
Okay.
斯坦
Stan?
我在
Hello?
谁啊
Who's that?
斯坦  是我
Stan. It's me.
滚出去
Get out of here.
我知道你现在很生我的气
Dude, I know you're pissed at me right now.
你要明白我那么做
You got to understand that I did it
是因为我心里明白
because I know in my heart
Xbox是我们最好的选择
that the Xbox is better for all of us.
你完全背叛了我们最后的一点友谊
You completely betrayed the last bit of friendship we still had.
你也耍手段了  哥们
You weren't playing fair, dude.
让你爸去商场太不公平了
Getting your dad to work part-time in the mall wasn't fair.
我根本就不知道  凯尔
I didn't even know he is working in the mall, Kyle.
真的吗
You didn't?
而你也会不直接来问我
But you couldn't have just asked me
因为Xbox人都不关心真相
because Xbox people don't care about the truth.
他们只关心无缝多媒体联接
They just care about seamless multimedia connectivity.
对不起  斯坦
I'm sorry, Stan.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这整个战争毁了我们俩
This whole war's just got us so screwed up.
我只是想用对的机器来玩《使命召唤》
I just want us to play Call of Duty on the right machine.
你不会明白的
You don't understand.
我再也不会跟你一起玩《使命召唤》了
I'm never playing Call of Duty with you again.
斯坦  别这么说啊
Stan, don't say that.
滚出去  我跟你玩完了
Get out of here. I'm done with you.
妈妈
Mom!
把他赶出去
Get him out of here!
快点
Get him out!
听着  现在就剩下我们八个了
Now listen up, there are only eight of us now.
彼得森是个好人
Peterson was a great guy
他不应该那样身首异处
and he did not deserve to get beheaded like that.
我不知道你们如何  我是受够了
Now I don't know about you but I am sick and tired of getting to
受够了去了解人们和他们的个性
know people here, getting invested on their personalities
他们的身世  然后看着他们死
and their backstory and then having them die.
那扇门打开之时  我们要团结一致
When those doors open, we all stick together.
谁胆怯了就将置我们于死地
If anyone panics, it puts us all at risk.
挺住  菜鸟
Stay tough, rookie.
我们挺不过去的  头儿
We're not going make it, sir.
我们能挺过去
We're going to make it!
你刚出生的小女儿
You've got a newborn little girl
需要她爸爸挺过去
who needs her daddy to make it.
我不会让你死的  好吗
I'm not going to let you die, okay?
好
Okay.
-好不好  -好的  头儿
- Okay? - Yes, sir.
好的  头儿
Yes, sir.
我不会再眼睁睁地看着一个好人死掉
Not one more good person dies on my watch.
天哪  他们从房顶进来了
Oh, my god, they're coming in through the roof!
我做不到
I can't do this.
对不起  我做不到
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
站住别动
Stay at your post.
不
No!
大家真的都很喜欢他
Everybody really liked him!
不
No!
开始了  汤姆
Here we go, Tom.
乔治・马丁终于到了
George R.R. Martin has finally arrived
来为超市剪彩
to cut the red ribbon.
女士们先生们  很荣幸今天早上来到这里
Ladies and gentlemen, it is my honor to be here this morning
代表南方公园超市合伙人  以及第九频道新闻
on behalf of south park mall partners and channel 9 news.
你的新闻  天气和体育媒体
Your go-to source for news, weather, and sports.
赶紧剪
Just do it.
很好
Very well.
依照祖祖辈辈的传统
In the tradition of our ancestors,
让我们欢庆节日的到来
Let's ring in the holidays!
但首先  关于我的鸡鸡有几句话想跟大家分享
But first I'd like to share with you a few words about my wiener.
南方公园超市
红罗宾餐厅
抱歉  红罗宾餐厅今天有特殊活动不营业
Sorry, guys, Red Robin is closed for a special event.
我们知道  我们是来参加婚礼的
We know, we're with the wedding.
好的  进去吧
Oh, great. Go right on in.
各位  各位  为黑色星期天干一杯
Everyone, everyone, a black friday toast.
我们又重归于好  真是太好了
How awesome that we're all friends again.
我们两大家族合二为一
Our two houses brought together.
很快我们都会有PS4了
Soon we'll all have our playstation 4s.
敬你  我的老朋友肯尼公主
And to you, my old friend, princess Kenny.
你看起来魅力难挡
You really look stunning.
毫无疑问上帝也会对着你的咪咪微笑
No doubt the gods have smiled down upon your perky boobs.
恕我失陪  公主殿下
Now if you'll excuse me, my lady,
我要去拉一泡屎
I need to take a shit.
你有什么发现
What have you found out?
超市还没开门
The mall isn't open yet.
他们在等乔治・马丁剪彩
They're waiting for george R.R. Martin to cut the ribbon.
好  那得有一阵子了
Okay. That could be a while.
我们的人都准备好了
All our men are ready.
超市一开门  就吹哨
When the mall opens, blow the whistle.
我们冲出去
We'll rush through the doors
把这帮索尼傻逼锁在里面
and lock the sony dorks inside.
好了  我真要去拉屎了
All right, now, I really do need to take a shit.
粉嫩的身体  紫色的脑袋
Oh, soft and pink with purple head,
你温柔地跟我在床上躺着
gently, you lay with me on my bed.
赶紧剪啊  乔治・马丁
Get on with it, George R.R. Martin!
嗷嗷  空中的鸡鸡咆哮起来
Growl, growl calls the wiener from on high,
小小鸡鸡  看上去特别可爱
a little tiny wiener still so pleasing to the eye.
别扯鸡巴蛋了
Enough with the wieners already.
快点
Yeah, come on!
克莱德
Clyde?
克莱德死哪去了
Where the hell is Clyde?
克莱德
Clyde?
肯尼公主  我觉得是时候
Princess kenny, I believe it's time
回敬巫师的款待了
we return the wizard's hospitality.
这是搞毛
What the hell is this?
抱歉  卡特曼
I'm sorry, Cartman.
计划有点小变化
There's been a little change in plan.
凯尔爵士  超市就要开门了
Sir, kyle, they're about to open the mall.
你干什么
What are you doing?
我不再是xbox这边的人了
I am no longer an xbox guy.
我害朋友关了禁闭
I let my friend get grounded.
但今天我会给他拿到PS
But today I will get him a playstation.
凯尔  PS的游戏柄烂透了  你是知道的
Kyle, the playstation controller sucks, and you know it!
战争结束了  卡特曼
The fight is over, Cartman.
还没有结束
It's not over.
看上去我来得正是时候
Looks like I came just in time.
比尔・盖茨  好样的
Oh, Bill Gates, sweet.
给你当头一棒  凯尔
In your face, Kyle.
你不准插手  比尔・盖茨
You will not interfere, Bill Gates!
这些孩子会得到PS4
These children will get their ps4s.
等等
Wait a minute.
这两个家伙怎么会在这
How the hell did these two guys end up here?
那不是你叛变计划的一部分吗
They're not part of your betrayal?
不是  那不是你叛变计划的一部分吗
No. They're not part of your betrayal?
不是
No.
那么这是谁的叛变计划
Who's betrayal is this?
我们不要再叛变了
We're done with betrayals.
是时候来个了结了
It's time to put an end to this.
斯坦
Stan?
头儿  上面说他们要我们一个人去
Sir, sir, operations just said they need one of us to
打开红罗宾的门
unlock the door to Red Robin to
让某个婚礼的人进入超市
let some wedding party inside the mall.
去他们的  让他们自己搞定
Screw them, they'll have to fend for themselves.
等等  红罗宾婚礼
Wait, Red Robin wedding?
谁要结婚
Who's getting married?
汤姆・汉克斯和碧昂丝
Tom Hanks and Beyonce.
什么
What?
天哪  人人都爱汤姆・汉克斯和碧昂丝
Oh, my god, everybody loves Tom Hanks and Beyonce!
我得去救他们
I got to save them
我感谢你试图做的一切  凯尔
I appreciate what you're trying to do,Kyle.
可我有更好的主意
But I have a better idea.
这不是我们的战争  伙计们
This isn't our war, you guys.
向来不是
It never was.
我们就为了俩公司的营销策略
We've been pitted against each other by two companies
而大打出手
for the sake of marketing.
所以他们要在街区设立分界线
That's why they want lines around the block.
他们需要战争好推销他们的产品
They want a war to promote their product.
他们才不管这会让多少友谊成为牺牲品
They don't give a crap what kind of friendship that costs.
你们这么想打仗吗
You want a war so bad,
那你俩打吧
then you fucking fight.
你我之间来个了结吧
Then let's finish this, you and me,
就在此地
right here.
开始了哟
胜者为王
Winner take all.
老兄  这下有好戏看了
Oh, dude, this is pretty sweet.
这将成为你最后一搏  比尔・盖茨
And this will be your last fight, Bill Gates.
伙计们  我错过了什么
Hey, guys, what did I miss?
瞧瞧这鸡鸡
Look at this wiener.
从它的尺寸来看
Judge it by its size.
撸三下就会有惊喜哟
Rub it three times and it has a surprise.
够了
That's it,
你休想再拖延  你这遛鸡鸡的混蛋
you're not delaying this any more, you wiener-loving bitch.
节日快乐  里克
Happy holidays, Rick.
你也是  我的朋友
And to you, my friend.
玩具市场
手办
抓住啊  瑞贝卡  抓住
Grab it, Rebecca, grab it!
都给老娘滚开
Kiss my fat vagina.
把那相机给我
Give me that camera.
快给我
Give me that.
回去  让开
Get back, get out of my way.
马什指挥官
Commander Marsh.
你知道你儿子本应该在家禁足
Did you know that your son is supposed to be grounded
却偷偷溜去了红罗宾吗
and snuck out to go to Red Robin?
什么
What?
斯坦也在红罗宾婚礼上吗
Stan's at the Red Robin wedding too?
天哪  我好担心他啊
Oh, God, I really care about him.
你就是这么死的
This is for how you die.
结束了
It's over.
Xbox赢了
Xbox WINS!
好耶  Xbox赢了
Yay, Xbox WINS.
好耶
Yay.
斯坦  你还活着呀
Stan, you're alive!
我救了你
I saved you!
没事了  碧昂丝  斗争结束了
It's okay, Beyonce, the fight's over.
你还能继续购物
You can still shop.
去吧  孩子们
Go on, kids.
去买Xbox吧
Go get your Xboxes.
艾蒙能闻一下你的蛋蛋吗
Can Elmo smell your genitals?
节日快乐
Happy holidays, guys.
你们想买什么
What can I interest you in?
我们想买Xbox One
We'd like to get Xbox Ones, please?
作出你的选择
有眼光
Good choice.
汤姆  疯狂购物结束了
Tom, the shopping frenzy is over
貌似微软的新Xbox One成为今年最热门的产品
and it looks like Microsoft's new Xbox One is this year's hot item.
毫无疑问  它将继续稳坐新一代游戏机的宝座
No dbout it will secure its place as the go to next gen console.
黑色星期五结束了
Black Friday is is over.
充斥着死亡  暴力  人性的丑恶
There's been death, violence, horrible human behavior
而最大的赢家  果断是第九频道新闻
and the big winner here decidedly is Channel 9 News.
界面太炫了
The interface is pretty cool.
我就说吧  它的界面天衣无缝
See, I told you guys it's really a... It's seamless interface.
是啊  的确
Yeah, it is.
画面要比老版本的Xbox清晰10%
The graphics are definitely like ten percent better than the old Xbox.
是啊  真不错
Yeah. That's pretty nice.
你们想出去玩玩什么的吗
You guys want to play outside or something?
卡特曼  你那边赢了
Cartman, your side won, dude.
干吗哭丧着脸
Why are you so sad?
我只是不停在回想比尔・盖茨
I just can't get the image of Bill Gates
猛打那家伙脑袋的场面
bashing that guy's head apart out of my eyes.
我明白你的意思
Yeah. I know what you mean.
伙计们  Xbox赢了游戏机之战
Look, guys, Xbox won the console wars, I mean,
那我们该怎么做  不打电子游戏了吗
what are we going to do, not play video games?
过去几个星期我们忙着
The last few weeks we've been
打电子游戏  瞧瞧我们都做了些什么
too busy to play video games and Look what we did.
上演了戏剧  动作片  爱情片
There's been drama, action, romance.
说实话  伙计们  咱们真的需要打游戏吗
I mean honestly, you guys, do we need video games to play?
是啊  他说得有道理
That's right. He's making a point.
或许我们开始太依赖微软和索尼  以至于
Maybe we started to rely on Microsoft and Sony so much that
忘记了我们要玩的不过是如此简单的东西
we forgot that all we need to play are the simplest things
比如这个
like...like this.
我们拿着这个就能玩了
We could just play with this.
去他妈的电子游戏
Screw video games.
我靠  谁稀罕啊
Dude, who fucking needs them?
去他妈的
Fuck'em.
南方公园
真理之杖
南方公园游戏
The South Park video game,
即将上架
coming to stores soon.
要是你连这都信
Yeah. If you believe that I have a
就等着我的大鸡鸡在你面前晃荡吧
big floppy wiener to dangle in your face.